Welcome
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): friends! This is cassette 4 of the introductory adult reading curriculum, Read4All. This cassette will introduce on-set letter sounds in context. Are you ready? Let's begin! A is for "Architecture".
The
Speaker 2: "Architecture" is delightful. B is for "Bees".
Speaker 2: Bees go buzz, buzz. C
is for
Speaker 2: cease and desist. Hey, stop it, now. D
is for delegitimatize. This
Speaker 2: debacle has really delegitimatized the work. E is for Egypt. The explorer explored the Egyptian plains.
F is
Speaker 2: for French. The French woman is a female. G
is for
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): glistened. The frozen ice glistened frozenly as the freezing temperature dropped to 30 degrees.
Speaker 2: H
is for
Speaker 2: hooray! Clip-clop-hooray! I is for Israel.
It's
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): good to know what is real and what is
not. J
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): is for "juicy". We all know the Jews see details no one else does. K is for "know". You know the line, but I'm not going to say
it. L
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): is for "literacy". Reading is literacy, and literacy is understanding.
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): An understanding is.
Speaker 2: M. M is for macabre. The burr real was quite mac-burr. N is for no. That's a no-no, kid. O is for officer. The special forces officer is a green barrette. P is for puzzle. Everything can be a puzzle.
Speaker 2: even if it isn't. Q is for
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): questions. Just asking questions is a clever way to make implications.
Speaker 4: R is for red yarn. Red yarn for
miles. S
Speaker 2: is for sleep pictures. While you sleep, mind movies give you
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): secrets. T is for thumb.
The
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): thumbtacks hold the red yarn in place. U is for unsubstantiated. An unsubstantiated claim can be solved by a hunch, vibe, or instinct.
V is for
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): victim. It's never too late to play the victim.
W is for
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): wine
Speaker 2: moms. Wine moms love true crime podcasts.
X
Speaker 2: is for Twitter. X is what some people call Twitter. Y is for yay. Even yay apologized. Z
is for
Speaker 2: zoinks. When
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): Shaggy and Scooby are trying to solve a case, they sometimes say zoinks. Great listening and learning. You're making excellent letter sounds. Remember,
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): Letters are like clues that when read correctly can help us make words. What clues did you find today? Listen again or refer to the transcript for additional practice. Turn over cassette tape to continue.
End of tape. End of tape. End of tape. End
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): of...